Guide to the Stan Steiner Papers, ca. 1940-1987 M0700
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series IV. Manuscripts by Others
  - Unidentified Working Papers for Edited Volume on New Mexico: V: Mexican American Religion n.d. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Series V. Notebooks
  - Notebook [1 of 3] 1942 [?] (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Notebook [2 of 3] 1942 [?] (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Notebook [3 of 3] 1942 [?] (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - In the Spring 1943 1943 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - In the Spring 1953 1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - [1953?] 1953 [?] (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Spring 1969 1969 Spring (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Al Pena Texas n.d. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The Building n.d. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Clyde, Vine, Clifton Hill notes NIYC, Maine, etc. n.d. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Governor David Cargo 1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Guadalupe Community Org. n.d. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Imperial Valley Fr. Garcia New Mexico villages n.d. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - La Raza notes n.d. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Leonard Muller, Director of Instructional Systems of IBM n.d. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - N.C.A.I. n.d. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Pre-7th n.d. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - San Joaquin Delana Ta Chimayo Gil Lopez Fresno n.d. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Tape transcription of Clyde and Clif Hill "Fran ken stein" notes n.d. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Mr. Vigil n.d. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Untitled n.d. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Untitled n.d. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Untitled n.d. (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Series VI. Reviews
  - New Indians [1 of 3] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - New Indians [2 of 3] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - New Indians [3 of 3] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - La Raza [1 of 4] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - La Raza [2 of 4] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - La Raza [3 of 4] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - La Raza [4of 4] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - La Raza [1 of 3] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - La Raza [2 of 3] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - La Raza [3 of 3] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - The Islands n.d. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Islands n.d. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - The Vanishing White Man n.d. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The Ranchers [1 of 3] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Ranchers [2 of 3] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Ranchers [3 of 3] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Spirit Woman n.d. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Fusang: Reviews n.d. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Fusang [1 of 2] c. 1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Fusang [2 of 2] c. 1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The Reviews n.d. (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Series VII. Business Files
  - Adair's Life and Times: Film Proposal to N.E.H. [1 of 4] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adair's Life and Times: Film Proposal to N.E.H. [2 of 4] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Adair's Life and Times: Film Proposal to N.E.H. [3 of 4] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Adair's Life and Times: Film Proposal to N.E.H. [4 of 4] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The American West 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - American Writers Congress [1 of 2] 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Writers Congress [2 of 2] 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Aztlán: Correspondence 1970 July 9-1972 Oct 19 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - College for Suki n.d. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Communal Housing--Brolin-Zeisel Urban Research & Design n.d. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Council for the Arts of Santa Fe c. 1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - County Tax Real Estate 1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Curtis Brown, Inc. [Knowlton, Perry H.] 1980 Nov 17 -1983 June 6 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Dark and Dashing Horsemen: Publicity [1 of 2] c. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Dark and Dashing Horsemen: Publicity [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Europe 1987 Summer (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Europe -- Contracts and Books 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Europe -- Editors' Letters 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Federal Taxes 1984 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - First Interstate Bank [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - First Interstate Bank [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Going Home, a Film for Hobel ["North With the Spring" Film Project] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Going Home, ["The Fabulous Sixties" Film Project] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Guggenheim Fellowships 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Income Tax 1979 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Income Tax 1981-1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - IncomeTax 1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "Indian Market in Santa Fe" Documentary [King, Mary Louise and King, Harry O.] 1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - In Search of the Jaguar ["The Jaguar and the Petrol: February Trip"]: Business Expenses and Correspondence n.d. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Insight Guide: Southwest [includes contract and correspondence from Virginia Hopkins] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Institute of the American West ["Inventing the West" [2 copies]] [1 of 2] 1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Institute of the American West ["Inventing the West" [2 copies]] [2 of 2] 1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Isleta Film of Zuni c. 1972 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - The Lantz Office, Inc. [Harris, Joy] 1983 Oct 24-Dec 27 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Las Vitas y Los Fotos -- Steiner's C.V., assorted photographs n.d. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - National Association and Center for Outlaw & Lawman History: Roster & Correspondence n.d. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - National Writers Union 1981 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - New Mexican Writers Co-operative n.d. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Paris [1 of 8] 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Paris [2 of 8] 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Paris [3 of 8] 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Paris [4 of 8] 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Paris [5 of 8] 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Paris [6 of 8] 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Paris [7 of 8] 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Paris [8 of 8] 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - P.E.N. Quarterly: Indian Writers 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Publicity for Steiner [column] n.d. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Santa Fe Council for the Arts n.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Southwest Studies, University of New Mexico n.d. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Steiner Vita n.d. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - THAMES TELEVISION [Devenish, Ross] 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - The Vanishing White Man: Movie [1 of 2] 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - The Vanishing White Man: Movie [2 of 2] 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - The Vanishing White Man: Publicity [1 of 2] 1976 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - The Vanishing White Man: Publicity [2 of 2] 1976 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Western Writers of America Conference 1982 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Western Writers of America Convention n.d. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Western Writers of America 29th Annual Convention, Santa Fe 1982 June 27-July 1 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Western Writers of America 29th Annual Convention, Bank Account 1982 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Western Writers of America 29th Annual Convention, Concert 1982 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Western Writers of America 29th Annual Convention, Expenses 1982 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Western Writers of America 29th Annual Convention, Staff 1982 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Addresses: Aloha n.d. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Addresses: Hungarian and Budapestian n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Addresses: The Islands [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Addresses: The Islands [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Addresses: La Raza [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Addresses: La Raza [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Addresses: the New Indians 1964-1970 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Addresses: The White Man n.d. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Addresses: Miscellaneous n.d. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Series VIII. Audiovisual Materials
  - Audiocassettes
    - In Search of the Jaguar: i. Maraeven Director Dr. Nelson Vasques / ii. Maraciapo n.d. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - In Search of the Jaguar: i. The Revolution of Intelligence, Machado / ii. same n.d. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - In Search of the Jaguar: i. Larry Vincente Delano and Farming / ii. Vincente - Rancho n.d. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - In Search of the Jaguar: Maraeven Refinery Director Coronel n.d. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - In Search of the Jaguar: Feminism y Venezuelan Woman: Dra. Garcia Maldonado n.d. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - In Search of the Jaguar: Claude Brun, Guayana n.d. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - In Search of the Jaguar: Monsenor Perez, Bishop of Caracas n.d. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - In Search of the Jaguar: i. Minister of Oil y Mines: Sr. Vanentin / ii. Levy Rossell, State of Culture n.d. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - In Search of the Jaguar: Jaji-Nicolas Vielma n.d. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - In Search of the Jaguar: Venezuelan Art Soto n.d. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - In Search of the Jaguar: i. Minister of Agriculture Gustavo Pinto Cohen / ii. Teatro Levy Rossell n.d. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - In Search of the Jaguar: Fed C. of C. Vogeler [?] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - In Search of the Jaguar: Maraeven, Carrdon Refinery, Withow, Production Chief n.d. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - In Search of the Jaguar: i. C. of C. Ven-Amer Galbado / ii. Fed C. of C. Vogeler n.d. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - The Ranchers: i. Skinner Ranch I: Ranch Policy / ii. Skinner Ranch II: Ranch Policy and Life n.d. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - The Ranchers: i. Ellen Cotton, Decker / ii. Ellen Cotton, Decker, Birds n.d. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - The Ranchers: i. Ruth and Janet Hill n.d. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - The Ranchers: Pettits, Texas, New Mexico n.d. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - The Ranchers: Marian and Frank Shiveley III n.d. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - The Ranchers: i. Bill Lumpkin, Ranch Life, 1911 / ii. Bill Lumpkin, Lincoln County and Family History n.d. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - The Ranchers: High Country News, Joan Nice n.d. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - The Ranchers: i. Sitz, Glenn, Oregon rancher / ii. Dr. Lou Attebury n.d. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - The Ranchers: i. Spragues, ranch, Colstrip, Rosebud Creek / ii. Wally McRae, Rocker Six, Cattle Co., Forsyth, Montana n.d. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - The Ranchers: i. Billy Stephenson, Barx / ii. Cauhape n.d. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - The Ranchers: i. Harry S. Chrisman, Denver '79, early pioneers in Nebraska, etc. / ii. Harry S. Chrisman, Western Writers 1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - The Ranchers: Elliott Barker n.d. (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - The Ranchers: Lamar, Howard - Indians, Yale n.d. (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - The Ranchers: i. Stan Jonasson, Idaho heritage / ii. Jonasson y Gino Clay S. Sky n.d. (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - The Ranchers: Jenny Vincent n.d. (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - The Ranchers: Shiveley, Frank and Marian - Nevada Mining and ranching n.d. (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - The Ranchers: Rex Bundy, ex-rodeo cowboy n.d. (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - The Ranchers: Cauhape n.d. (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - The Ranchers: Fred Turner n.d. (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - The Ranchers: Gerald Allen, Juntura Ranch n.d. (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - The Ranchers: i. Writers in Missoula bar - Annick Smith and Bill Kittredge / ii. Dr. Myers: Research Lib. Montana Historical Society n.d. (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - The Ranchers: Glenn Sitz - Oregon Rancher n.d. (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - The Ranchers: Skinner Ranch - Personal Life n.d. (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - The Ranchers: Roberta Cheney, WWA, Cameron, Montana / ii. Terri Axe, MPRC, Billings n.d. (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - The Vanishing White Man: i. Rev. Kent Mallard, Church and Indian Spirit / ii. Rapid City, S.D. 1973 Oct. (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - The Vanishing White Man: Wounded Knee 1973 Oct. (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - The Vanishing White Man: Big Sky Mine foreman, Montana stuff 1973 Oct. (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - The Vanishing White Man: i. Del McBride, Olympia, Washington / ii.Cannon - Natural Resources Oregon Assistant to the Governor 1973 July (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - The Vanishing White Man: Ceremonial History - Merry, Gallup and Indian Art 1974 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - The Vanishing White Man: i. City Manager of Callup to '60 / ii. Ceremonial Gallup Merry 1974 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - The Vanishing White Man: The Hopi Prophecy Vice Chairman Alvin Dashee 1974 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - The Vanishing White Man: Media and Indian Lovers, Mifaunway Shunatona, New York 1974 May (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - The Vanishing White Man: Indian Market, Santa Fe 1973 Aug. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The Vanishing White Man: Dr. Fred Dockstader, Museum of American Indian, New York 1974 June (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - The Vanishing White Man: South Dakota Lawyer, Rapid City 1973 Oct. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - The Vanishing White Man: Fake Indian jewelery, Sunbell, Albuquerque / ii. Locato and Baca 1974 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - The Vanishing White Man: Fake Indian jewelery, Sunbell, Albuuquerque 1974 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - The Vanishing White Man: Senator James Abouresk, Washington, D.C. 1974 May (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - The Vanishing White Man: Wounded Knee - i. Aim story, ii. Veterans 1973 Spring (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - The Vanishing White Man: Bob Ward, Santa Fe, NM 1975 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - The Vanishing White Man: Gerry Wilkinson 1975 Summer (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - The Vanishing White Man: Boyd Charter, Montana rancher 1973 Oct. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - The Vanishing White Man: Tom Bell, High Country News, Lander, Wyoming 1973 Oct. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - The Vanishing White Man: Land use and energy - Interior Secretary Wally Hickel 1973 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - The Vanishing White Man: Frank Diluzio, Governor's Science advisor 1974 Sept. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - The Islands: Herman Flores, Young Lords 1973 Winter (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - The Islands: Herman Flores, Young Lords, Bronx, New York 1973 Winter (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - The Islands: Father David Garcia, St. Marks, New York City 1973 Winter (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Reel-to-Reel Cassettes
    - The Islands: Alegría, Dr. Ricardo, Institute of Puerto Rican Culture, San Juan 1971 Apr. 19 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - The Islands: Benitz, Jaime, President, University of Puerto Rico 1971 Sept. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - The Islands: Berrios, Ruben, P.I.P. 1971 Sept. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - The Islands: Bishop Parrilla, The Church 1971 Sept. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - The Islands: Bras, Sr. Mari, MPI Independence Movement, San Juan 1971 Apr. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - The Islands: Bras, Sr. Mari, MPI, San Juan 1971 Apr. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - The Islands: Chicago - Figueroa, R.A.V. 1971 Sept. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - The Islands: Chicago - Rodriguez, Ben 1971 Sept. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - The Islands: Chicago - Torres de Jesus 1971 Sept. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - The Islands: Chicago Barrio - Diaz, A. 1971 Sept. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - The Islands: Chicago Barrio - Division Street 1971 Sept. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - The Islands: Chicago Youth - Colon, Beatrice 1971 Sept. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - The Islands: Dr. Costa, Lincoln Hospital n.d. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - The Islands: Diaz, Manuel, New York 1972 Mar. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - The Islands: Feliciano, Carlos, Nationalist Party n.d. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - The Islands: Ferre, Governor Luis, San Juan 1971 Sept. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - The Islands: Police Inspector Fink, New York 1972 Apr. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - The Islands: Gerena Valentin, NY Scene 1972 Mar. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - The Islands: Hernandez Colon, Rafael, President, Puerto Rican Senate, San Juan 1972 Apr. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - The Islands: Hostos College - Candido de Leon 1972 May (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - The Islands: Lugo, Nick, Commissioner of Migration, New York 1972 Mar. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - The Islands: Lugo, Nick, Commissioner of Migration, New York 1972 Mar. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - The Islands: Matos, Don Pedro - history and agriculture 1971 Sept. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - The Islands: Matos, Don Pedro - mining and [?], Utuado 1971 Apr. 21 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - The Islands: Matos, Don Pedro - Puerto Rican Indian history, Utuado 1971 Apr. 21 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - The Islands: Oliver, Denise, Young Lords Party, New York 1971 Feb. 22 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - The Islands: Oliver, Denise, Young Lords Party, New York 1971 Feb. 22 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - The Islands: Puerto Rican women - Ramos, Emma 1971 May (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - The Islands: Resident Commissioner - Cordova, Washington, D.C. 1972 Mar. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - The Islands: San Juan Barrios 1971 Apr. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - La Raza: Alianza, Mercure, Padilla, Crusade for Justice, Corky Gonzales, Grace Olivarez n.d. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - La Raza: Alvarado, Maggie n.d. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - La Raza: i. Barraza, Maclouio / ii. Rameriz, Jose n.d. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - La Raza: La Cesar n.d. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - La Raza: Chavez, WBAI n.d. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - La Raza: Chavez, Cesar at Delano, California n.d. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - La Raza: Chavez, Cesar book n.d. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - La Raza: Chavez, Fabian 1972 Dec. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - La Raza: Chicano kids in El Paso; machismo n.d. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - La Raza: Citizens Hunger inquiry n.d. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - La Raza: Corona 1967 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - La Raza: Corona, Bert, President Mexican American Political Association [MAPA] n.d. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - La Raza: Debate on Help-Cap Poverty Program, Anton Chico, N.M. n.d. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - La Raza: East L.A. and Delano, CA n.d. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - La Raza: Four young guys from L.A. 1968 July (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - La Raza: Gonzales, Corky - Crusade for Justice and MExicanos politics n.d. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - La Raza: Gonzales, Corky - II n.d. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - La Raza: Guiterrez, Gustavo n.d. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - La Raza: Huerta, Dolores n.d. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - La Raza: Huerta, Dolores n.d. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - La Raza: Huerta, Dolores - II (copy) 1967 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - La Raza: i. Matta, Paul / ii. Lozada and Davilla, Donna, Texas n.d. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - La Raza: Murieta n.d. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - La Raza: New Mexico EPA - Bond, Aaron and Gordon, Larry 1972 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - La Raza: Olivarez, Grace n.d. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - La Raza: i. Padilla, Gilberto / ii. Mr. Rodriguez n.d. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - La Raza: Pedrazza, Miguel, Governor of Tigua n.d. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - La Raza: Perez, Eddie n.d. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - La Raza: Sandoval, George - woodcarving n.d. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - La Raza: Tijerina, Reies Lopez n.d. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - La Raza: Tijerina, Reies Lopez n.d. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - La Raza: Tijerina at Alianza office after he got out of prison 1967 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - La Raza: Valdez, Fecundo 1967 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - La Raza: Valdez, Luis in Delano, California 1968 -1969 Summer [?] (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - La Raza: Valdez, Luis n.d. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - La Raza: i. Vigil, Cleofus - Indian creation story / ii. Garcia, Lauro, Guadalupe, Arizona n.d. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - La Raza: Vigil, Cleofus of San Cristobal n.d. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - La Raza: Yellen, Dr. Sam - Imperial Valley irrigation controversy n.d. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - La Raza: untitled n.d. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Motion Pictures
    - The American Indian Speaks. Chicago: The Encyclopedia Britannica Educational Corporation n.d. (Box 12, Folder 1)
      1 film reel (22 min.): magnetic, sd., col.; 16 mm.
    - The Water is so clear, that a Blind man could see. release print n.d. (Box 12, Folder 2)
      1 film reel: magnetic; 16 mm.
    - What has happened to the American Indians. English soundtrack n.d. (Box 13, Folder 1)
      1 sound track film reel: magnetic; 16 mm.
    - What has happened to the American Indians. Visuals n.d. (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Series IX. Clippings
  - Aboriginal Peoples n.d. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - African-Americans n.d. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Central & South America n.d. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Communists & Soviet Union n.d. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Drugs n.d. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Energy (1 of 3) n.d. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Energy (2 of 3) n.d. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Energy (3 of 3) n.d. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Entertainment n.d. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Environmentalism (1 of 2) n.d. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Environmentalism (2of 2) n.d. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Land Use & Property Law (1 of 2) n.d. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Land Use & Property Law (2 of 2) n.d. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Law Enforcement (1 of 2) n.d. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Law Enforcement (2 of 2) n.d. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Literature & Arts (1 of 2) n.d. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Literature & Arts (2 of 2) n.d. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Native America (1 of 6) n.d. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Native America (2 of 6) n.d. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Native America (3 of 6) n.d. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Native America (4 of 6) n.d. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Native America (5 of 6) n.d. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Native America (6 of 6) n.d. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - New Mexico & the Southwest (1 of 2) n.d. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - New Mexico & the Southwest (2 of 2) n.d. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Nixon Administration (1 of 2) n.d. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Nixon Administration (2 of 2) n.d. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Politics (General) (1 of 2) n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Politics (General) (2 of 2) n.d. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Prostitution n.d. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Puerto Rico & Latino Culture n.d. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Technology & Industry n.d. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - American West n.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Youth Culture (1 of 2) n.d. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Youth Culture (2 of 2) n.d. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous (1 of 4) n.d. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous (2 of 4) n.d. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous (3 of 4) n.d. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous (4 of 4) n.d. (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Series X. Lectures and Academe
  - Cowboy Culture: Class at University of New Mexico, Department of American Studies [includes correspondence] 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cowboy Culture: lectures [includes correspondence] 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cowboy Culture: carbons [student papers] [1 of 5] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cowboy Culture: carbons [student papers] [2 of 5] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cowboy Culture: carbons [student papers] [3 of 5] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Cowboy Culture: carbons [student papers] [4 of 5] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Cowboy Culture: carbons [student papers] [5 of 5] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Indian visuals 1967 -1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lecture notes n.d. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Lecture on Macho [1 of 3] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Lecture on Macho [2 of 3] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Lecture on Macho [3 of 3] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Lecture on Macho n.d. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Letter and dates 1976 -1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - National Honors seminar on the Southwest n.d. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Native Studies, University of California, Berkeley 1976 -1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - New Mexico lectures n.d. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Publicity 1981 -1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - University of New Mexico Undergraduate Seminar program 1974 -1975 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Visual materials 1975 -1977 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Series XI. Publications
  - Aguirre, Rueben E. "Education of the Mexican American Child in Language Development" Denver, CO 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Ethnological Society. "Spanish-Speaking People in the United States" 1968 Annual Spring Meeting 1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Indian Law Newsletter.--Vol. 7, no. 10 (1974 June 24) 1974 June 24 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Indian Law Newsletter.--Vol. 7, no. 16 (1974 Aug. 30) 1974 Aug. 30 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - American Indian Law Newsletter.--Vol. 7, no. 20 (1974 Oct. 25) 1974 Oct. 25 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - American Indian Press Association New Service Press Releases [1 of 4] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Indian Press Association New Service Press Releases [2 of 4] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - American Indian Press Association New Service Press Releases [3 of 4] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - American Indian Press Association New Service Press Releases [4of 4] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - The American West 1975 Jan. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Among the Clouds, Mt. Washington, NH.--Vol. 23, no. 38 (1899 Aug. 26) 1899 Aug. 26 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Apache Scout.--Vol. 1, no. 5 (1974 May) 1974 May (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Arizona Commission of Indian Affairs Annual Report 1972 -1973 (Box 1, Folder 13)